Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs, ca. 1950s-2007 AIS.2013.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Prints and Negatives, ca. 1950s-2004; II.
  - Early Career, ca. 1950s; 2.
    - Portraits, November 3, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 83)
  - Murray "Buzzy" Susser, 1963-1980; 3.
    Harris followed University of Pittsburgh medical student Murray "Buzzy" Susser as he trained to be an astronaut. Though the story was originally shot for the January 1963 issue of Pitt Magazine, Susser and Harris developed a friendship and Harris continued to photograph their families and important personal events. This series contains prints, negatives, the January 1963 edition of Pitt Magazine, and mounted prints.
    - Negatives, ca. 1960s-1980s (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Subjects include: Stadium from Air; Pregnant Julie and Buzzy; Buzzy, Judy and Eva; New York: Buzzy and Girl; Buzzy and Family: Baltimore; Buzzy at Home, Party; Buzzy in New York City; Buzzy and Julie at Elmcrest Manor, Connecticut; Buzzy and Kids; Buzzy and Noose; Baby Julie; Buzzy in California.
    - Buzzy's Wedding Photographs; Buzzy and the Ice Cream Truck, ca. 1960s (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Buzzy and Kyp: Toy Airplanes, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Pitt Magazine: Buzzy Cover Story, January 1963 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Buzzy and Kyp: In Hospital, Julie Just Born, ca. 1960s (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Portraits of Buzzy Susser, November 20, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Buzzy Military Training, ca. 1960s (Box 51, Folder 7-8, 12)
    - Buzzy at Home, ca. 1960s (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Buzzy and Kyp: Wedding, ca. 1960s (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Buzzy Military Training; At Home with Family, ca. 1960s (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Garbage Stories, ca. 1960s; 4.
    In the early 1960, Harris photographed Pittsburgh garbage men as they collected trash and interacted with the community. Focusing mainly on one man, Mr. Barksdale, Harris documented the day-to-day work and personal lives of a specific group of city employees. This collection overlaps with a small series of photographs taken on one roll of film of a homeless man digging through trash in downtown Pittsburgh. Harris named the two groups of images "Garbage Stories."
    - Negatives, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Digital Prints, July 15, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 3, 7)
    - Narrative of "Man and Garbage Series" by Barbara Paul, 2002; Alan Lefkowitz, consultant at law. Agreement for "Sale of Fine Art Photography." (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Prints for Exhibition, July 15, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 5, 8)
    - Large Mounted Prints (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Chronological, 5.
    - ca. 1950s/1960s
      - Portrait of a Woman; Bridge; Bikes; Living Room; Jack Brown; David and Lorraine; Bridge and Road Construction, ca. 1950s/1960s (Box 47, Folder 76)
      - Glickman: Steve; Nestie and Ryna at Carnegie Mellon University Archway and Dark Haired Girl; Murray "Buzzy" Susser's Niece under a Table; Girl on Pitt Nutrition Poster; Betty at Carnegie Mellon University; Hannah in Hood; Betty Reisenstein in Ruins; Hannah in Ruins; Murray "Buzzy" Susser and Preachers on the Street; Pamela in Jackie's Kitchen; Alvin and Pamela; Murray "Buzzy" Susser's Niece and Murray "Buzzy" Susser in Medical School Movie, ca. 1950s (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Jack Brewin, ca. 1950s (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Tandy at Carnegie Mellon University, Ron Rosenberg Wedding, ca. 1950s (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Alfa Romeo Veloce Spirit, Corvette, and Porsche, ca. 1950s/1960s (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - ca. 1960s
      - David Susser, ca. 1960s (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Murray "Buzzy" Susser Portrait and Kyp Wedding, Lens Test: Maria, Squirrel Hill Shops, Forbes Avenue, Incline: Koppers and Gulf Buildings from Civic Arena, Phone Booth, Koppers: Bud at Work, ca. 1960s (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Woman in White Shirt, ca. 1960s (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Jacke's Party; Barry's Mothers; Dave's Class, New York and Alvin; Marsha; Law Library; Bridges; Fireworks at The Point; Scoreboard at Kaufmann's 1962 US Open; Mat Wheel Unlimited, ca. 1960s (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Steel Mill Guys and Baby Mathew; Baby Mathew and J&L Steel Mill, Cleveland; Stickle and Bachman 100 Years Old; Stan Sobel and Stickle; Party Outside Bruce Hall, and Guitar, ca. 1960s (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Homeless Man Project, ca. 1960s (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - 1964
      - Pitt: Bradford Campus, May 1964 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - 1967
      - Oakland Row Houses, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - 1968
      - Pittsburgh March on the National Day of Mourning for MLK, April 7, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - 1970s
      - Patio Pictures and Carnival, ca. 1970s (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - 1970
      - Peter Berndtson's Houses for Exhibition at Frick, Aaron Shoen, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 33)
        Negatives include: Balter House (Berndtson), Blum House, Duncan House (Frank Lloyd Wright), Polymath Park, Usonian Houses.
      - Paul and Kids: Cemetery, Roll 4 (Job # 93070), September 30, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - 1969-1971
      - Social Security Administration, 1969-1971 (Box 48, Folder 31)
      - Social Security Administration, 1969-1971 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - 1972
      - Mackenzie's Dairy Ice Cream: Larry Mackenzie, June 7, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - 1973
      - Dresser, Harbison Walker Refractories Company, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 48)
      - Railroad Timbers, April 5, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 51)
      - Social Security Administration, May 21, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 52)
      - Koppers: Faces, 14, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Koppers: Faces, Rolls 1-10, 12, 13, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 15-16)
      - Koppers: Railroad Ties Production, September 1973 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Koppers: Driveway Sealing, September 1973 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - 1975
      - Oxford Development Corporation: Monroeville Mall, January 1975 (Box 48, Folder 59)
        Additional negatives available at Job # 23407
      - Lynn Venetoulis Campaign, April 1975 (Box 48, Folder 60)
      - Kurlinski Family, May 27, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 63)
      - Koppers, July 18, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 86)
      - Ron Rothfus- Personal, March 19, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 87)
    - 1976
      - Florida, April 28, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 66)
      - Bike Jumping, October 26, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 67)
    - 1977
      - Rockwell Bathroom Fixture Display, January 26, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 80)
      - Koppers (Houston-Dallas), April 12, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 82)
      - Koppers, June 24, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 79)
      - Bob Koehler, October 13, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 81)
      - Giant Stadium, August 1, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 82)
    - 1978
      - Koppers, January 9, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 83)
      - Koppers, April 12, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 84)
      - Koppers, May 24, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 85)
    - 1981
      - Bike Race and Skier, January 1981 (Box 47, Folder 80)
    - 1984
      - Koppers: Abe Lincoln Statue, Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), and Bob O'Gara, October 30, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - 1990s
      - Archadeck: Staff Pictures and Decks, ca. 1990s (Box 48, Folder 85)
    - 1990
      - Koppers: Oxnard and Petrolia, June 28, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 87)
      - Koppers: Plant, August 10, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 88)
    - 1991
      - Archadeck: Cecil Champagne, July 19, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 89)
    - 1992
      - Beazer: Staff Photo, February 3, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 90)
    - 1994
      - Thrift Drug Classic, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Hickson Corporation Orchard, June 2, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Alcoa: Paul O'Neil on Christmas, December 31, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 2001
      - Koppers: Wall, Pennsylvania Yards, Koppers Turnout, February 2001 (Box 49, Folder 41)
      - Koppers: Guthrie, Oklahoma, February 2001 (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - French Drain Waterproofing, August 13, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - 2003
      - Koppers: Remsa Dallas, May 5, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - 2004
      - Koppers: Portrait of Leslie Hyde, June 4, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 43)
      - Koppers: Portrait of Tony Niederberger, June 8, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 44)
      - Koppers: Portrait of Tony Loadman, June 8, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Undated
      - Pitt: Physical Education Building, Dental School (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Pitt: Larry Rosiek Portrait (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Telephone Poles (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Alvin Rounce and Motorcycle, Jakie (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Archadeck (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Sandy Kaufman: 1326 Murray, 6 Houses from Wilkins (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Howard's Painting (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Simma and Roland Kindhart (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Tandy at Carnegie Mellon University (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Portrait of Mat, BMX Bike Race (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Four Girls Project (Box 47, Folder 28)
      - Women (Box 47, Folder 31)
        These prints were found dispersed throughout the collection and have been gathered by subject.
      - Roz Litman: Kids, Portraits (Box 47, Folder 32)
      - Portrait of a Woman (Box 47, Folder 35)
      - Wayne Kurlinski Portrait (Box 47, Folder 36)
      - New York, South Park, Judy Ross (Box 47, Folder 37)
      - Gateway Rehabilitation Center (Box 47, Folder 41)
        This folder contains: Prints, Negatives, Slides and paper documents.
      - Tumi at the Point (Box 47, Folder 42)
      - Archadeck (Box 47, Folder 48)
      - Cement in Pipe (Box 47, Folder 49)
      - Bud in Mirror with Camera, Wayne K and Helen Knox, Murray "Buzzy" Susser and Kyp (Pregnant) (Box 47, Folder 50)
      - Dr. Thomas: Retouched Print and Negative (Box 47, Folder 54)
      - Widelux, Denniston, Susie, Jeff Blur (Box 47, Folder 55)
      - Eva's Birthday, Parkway Construction (Box 47, Folder 56)
      - Various Portraits (Box 47, Folder 64)
      - Davey Susson, Graduation from Pitt (Box 47, Folder 69)
      - Koppers: Inside Plant (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Koppers: Photographs of Bud (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Prints, ca. 1950s-2004; III.
  Subjects documented within this series include University of Pittsburgh, Chatham University, J&L Steel, Byrd Brown, Thrift Drug Classic, Art Swiden, BMX, Carnegie Museum of Art, Koppers, Gateway, Photo Maxima, PPG, Panther Hollow, MLK, Social Security Administration, Europe, Rutgers University, Disney World, American Express, Hickson and Archadeck.
  - On Location Show, 2.
    Images in this subseries are mounted on foam board with Velcro on the back for hanging. The entire show is housed within Box 68.
    - Installation Photograph (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - "Lunch in Gateway" and "Silent Man", 1964, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - "Logging in British Columbia" and "Train to Paris", 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - "Building the Parkway" and "Pamela-Drama Student", 1958, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - "Homeless Markey Square" "Southside Girl and Clothesline" and "Italian Entrepreneur", 1958, 1960, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - "Businessmen of Milan" and "Silent Man", 1964, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - "Names on the Wall," and Homeless Man, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - "Man of Iron" and "Boys in City School Yard", 1964, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Chronological, 1.
    - ca. 1950s
      - Gateway Pictures, ca. 1950s (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Ryna and Alvin, ca. 1950s (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Photo Maxima Exhibition Contact Sheet, ca. 1950s (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Newman Schmidt: Woman in Kitchen, ca. 1950s (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Stevenson Peanuts, ca. 1950s (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - 1957
      - Photo Maxima Installation, March 22-31, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 10)
        Photograph by Hope Sanders.
    - ca. 1960s
      - Lens Test, ca. 1960s (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Julie, Emil, Movie, David Susser, ca. 1960s (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - 1961
      - Ketcham, Macleod and Grove Inc., July 7, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - 1962
      - PPG Fiber Glass Advertisement, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - 1963
      - Contact Sheets and Documents, Pitt Freshman, December 6, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - 1964
      - Carnegie Museum of Art: International, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Panther Hollow Project, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 20-21)
      - Panther Hollow Project, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - 1968
      - Pittsburgh March on the National Day of Mourning for MLK, April 7, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 25-26)
      - Pittsburgh March on the National Day of Mourning for MLK, April 7, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Pittsburgh March on the National Day of Mourning for MLK, April 7, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - J&L Steel Research, Art Institute Weaving Show, April 8, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - 1969
      - Social Security Administration, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 28)
      - Social Security Administration, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - ca. 1970s
      - Europe Trip, ca. 1970s (Box 47, Folder 77)
      - Europe Trip, ca. 1970s (Box 52, Folder 11, 14)
      - Europe Trip, ca. 1970s (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Rutgers University, 1974/1975 (Box 53, Folder 78)
    - 1970
      - Byrd Brown for Congress, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Byrd Brown for Congress: Campaign Materials, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 32)
      - Contact Sheets, September 30, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - 1971
      - Peter Portrait, Steenberg House, February 21, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 36)
      - The Balter House, February 25, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 37)
      - Sempeon Deck (Contact Sheets), October 25, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 38)
      - Koppers: Fletcher L. Byrom, July 8, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Koppers, July 27, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - 1972
      - Wen Schmidt, I.M.G., Judy Fender Nurses, February 11, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 41)
      - Lando, B. Mandel, Portsmouth Ohio, Foam Cup, July 25, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 43)
      - Foam Cups Advertising, September 28, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 45)
      - Koppers: Toledo Lam Beam, April 17, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Koppers, August 22, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Koppers: Basketball Court, September 25, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - 1973
      - Contact Sheets, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 46)
      - Pittsburgh Marathon, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 47)
      - Dresser, Harbison Walker Refractories Company, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 49)
      - Petrolia Plant, February 1, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 50)
      - Baltimore Harbor, June 29, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 53)
      - Real Estate Family, June 26, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 54)
      - Koppers: Machinery, January 11, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Koppers: Perfect Pine Tree, January 16, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Koppers: Luncheon, January 25, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Koppers: Laminated, Briarlake Baptist Church, Decatur Georgia, March 29, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Koppers: Wrenton Calrd Oven, May 11, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Koppers: Jim Pisarick, May 11, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Koppers, August 15, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Koppers: Roof Tar, August 21, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - 1974
      - Fish/Water Testing by Nuclear Plant, February 15, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 55)
      - Wood Shop, May 25, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 56)
      - Rutgers University, November 2, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 57)
        No Images, only folders.
    - 1975
      - Clifford Development Corporation: Monroeville Mall, (Job # 23407), January 1975 (Box 48, Folder 58)
      - African American Office Workers, April 17, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 62)
      - Railroad Timbers, April 5, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 61)
      - Koppers: Stadium Construction, February 11, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - Koppers, October 1, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - 1976
      - Koppers, March 1, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - 1977
      - Koppers: Barb Portrait, 1976/1977 (Box 48, Folder 68)
      - Bob Kohler, August 15, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 69)
      - Bob Kohler, October 12, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 70)
    - 1978
      - Fletcher L. Byrom Lecture, May 10, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 71)
      - BMX Racing, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 72)
      - BMX, Mat, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 73)
      - BMX Indoor Track, S. Panex Silberg, Job #. 6811, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 74)
      - Koppers: Wood Decking, Pensacola, Florida, May 24, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - 1979
      - Black Africa Activities: Barbara Gunn, December 19, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 75)
      - Koppers, August 29, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - Koppers: Boston Marathon, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 32-33)
    - 1980
      - BMX Indoor Track, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 76)
      - Chatham College: WQED Minna Kaufmann Ruud Award, April 14, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 77)
      - BMX: John Serefini (Client), Stephenson Agency, 5th and Wood, September 16, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 78)
      - Eye and Ear Hospital, September, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 79)
      - Koppers: Wood Decking at Zoo, Montreal, Canada, May 23, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - Disney World for American Express: Production Shots, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - 1988
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, September 29, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - 1989
      - Wood, November 6, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 82)
      - Hickson Corporation, Charleston, November 6, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 83)
    - ca. 1990s
      - Thrift Drug Classic, ca. 1990s (Box 48, Folder 84)
      - Hickson Corporation Deck, ca. 1990s (Box 48, Folder 86)
    - 1992
      - Archadeck, October 29, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 91-97)
        Subjects include: Madison Wood, Pressure Treated Wood, and Koppers.
    - 1993
      - Hickson Corporation, September 24, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - 1995
      - Alcoa, October 23, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - 1996
      - Pittsburgh Flood, January 21, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - SMC Mary Hendel, July 2, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Alcoa: Day of Caring, Ligonier Boyscout Camp, September 19, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Hickson Deck, October 1996 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Thrift Drug Classic, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Koppers, October 8, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - 1998
      - Archadeck, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Archadeck, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - 2000
      - Koppers: Railroad Track, April 19, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - Koppers: Railroad Track, April 19, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 39)
      - Koppers: Balcas, September 12, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - 2004
      - Koppers: 20th Floor Lobby Display, November 18, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 46)
      - Children, July 16, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - 2006
      - Diane Litmas, March 6, 2006 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - 2007
      - August Wilson Center Show, March 19, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 22)
      - Frick Fine Arts Submission, May 2007 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Undated
      Box 67 contains oversized and large mounted prints.
      - Pitt: Frick Oakland, Church Board (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Pitt: Posvar (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Pitt: Students, Campus Life, Portraits (Vintage Prints) (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Pitt: Students, Campus Life, Portraits (Digital Prints) (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Pitt: Pitt Magazine (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Chatham College (Box 47, Folder 8-9)
      - House by the Train Tracks (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - J&L Steel Mill Cleveland (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Children (Box 47, Folder 18, 58)
      - Politicians (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Girl with Freckles (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Blonde Girl with Flowers in a Bedroom (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - Suzie (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - Mat, Suzie and Maria (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - Woman with Brown Hair (Box 47, Folder 29)
      - Woman with Short Hair (Box 47, Folder 30)
      - Railroad Crane (Box 47, Folder 33)
      - Charles "Cheech" Litman at the "Coin Exchange", Grant Building (Box 47, Folder 34)
      - Larry Rosiek (Box 47, Folder 38)
      - Small Mounted Prints: Man with Cigarette, Woman in a Dark Room, Man in Greenhouse, Cathedral of Learning, Mural in Pitt Building, Man Downtown, Girl by "Woman" Door, Man by Gate, Woman Smiling by Tree, Woman in Shadows (Box 47, Folder 39)
      - Thrift Drug Classic (Box 47, Folder 40)
      - Stephen Schwartz (Box 47, Folder 43)
      - Pittsburgh (Box 47, Folder 44-45, 53, 61)
      - Judy Parker: Eye Magazine and Portraits, Barry Seltzer Studio in New York City (Box 47, Folder 47)
      - Art Swiden: Boxer Training (Box 47, Folder 51)
      - BMX Bike and Mat (Box 47, Folder 52)
      - Europe (Digital Prints) (Box 47, Folder 59)
      - New York City (Digital Prints) (Box 47, Folder 60)
      - Unidentified Prints (Box 47, Folder 62-63)
      - Steel Manufacturing (Box 47, Folder 65)
      - Road Construction (Box 47, Folder 66)
      - Home for Children, Hospital (Box 47, Folder 68)
      - Logging (Box 47, Folder 70)
      - Man in Washington, D.C. (Box 47, Folder 71)
      - Pictures of Bud (Box 47, Folder 72)
      - Bud as a Boy (Box 47, Folder 73)
      - Carnegie Museum of Art (Box 47, Folder 74)
      - Koppers: Various Unidentified Prints (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Contact Sheets (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Koppers (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases and Prints (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Steel Manufacturing (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Pittsburgh City Views (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Four Girls Project (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Boy on a Hill (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Old Woman and Children, Panther Hollow, Man at Desk (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Gog Magog and Babylon, Factory Workers, Bottles (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Bridgework (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Koppers: Baltimore, Inner Harbor (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Children (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Hospital (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Women (Box 67, Folder 2, 13, 15)
      - University of Pittsburgh: Mural in Frick Fine Arts Building, Science Lab and Filing Cabinets (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Railroad Downtown (Box 67, Folder 17-18)
      - Children: Mat, Mat and Maria, Social Security Administration Children in Graveyard (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Women (Box 67, Folder 2, 6)
      - Portraits (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Portraits: Bud Self Portrait in Mirror, Pitt Student Blowing Bubbles, Makeup in Mirror, Portrait of a Man Pointing (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Portraits of Children (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Trees (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Maria (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Large Mounted Prints (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Oversized Prints: Self Portrait, Social Security Administration, Children, Concert, Parkway, Boy on Hill (Map-case 7-6, Folder 1)
      - Political Posters: Byrd Brown, Pete Flaherty, Poor People's Campaign (MLK), 1968-1970 (Map-case 7-6, Folder 2)
      - Oversized Mounted Prints (Map-case 7-6, Folder 3)
      - Contact Sheets (Box 80, Folder 24-38)
- Slides, ca. 1960s-2003; IV.
  Slides in this series were primarily found in slide carousels for presentations. They have been removed from the carousels, but stored in the same order as the presentations. Those not part of presentations are titled with subject matter or job title. All slides are arranged between two subseries of dated and undated. Topics include: Blue Diamond Materials, Styrofoam Cups, Koppers, South Side Drug and Alcohol, Gateway, IABC, American Express, Fritz Goro, Three Rivers Stadium, St. Peters, Social Security Administration, Wightman Manor, Milltown, La Normande Restaurant, BMX, Sully Miller, Hickson, Alcoa, Thrift Drug Classic, and the City of Pittsburgh.
  - Steinberg, Marshall, Balter, Blum: Architecture, February 3, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - "3 Black Boys Profile", September 1, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - Howard's Painting (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Blue Diamond Materials; Sloan Const., Co., Greenville, South Carolina; The Stone Man Inc., Murfreesboro, Texas; Nello L. Teer Company; Koppers: Interior Building and People Shots; Kaiser Sand and Gravel Company; BPS Baldwin Bridgeville; Koppers: Norfolk Southern Wood; Koppers: Management Talk; Koppers; Airport Extras; Archadeck: Rob Kronck, Cleveland Office (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Styrofoam Job; Pittsburgh Airport: Outside; Railroad: Old Photographs of Station Square (Historic pictures, not Bud's photographs.) (Box 54, Folder 2)